脆莓医疗中心 Kuzniak医生坐诊
Woody 你的结肠镜检查结果出来了
Woody, I have the results of your colonoscopy.
说实话 大夫 我得了屁癌了吗?
Be honest, doc. Do I have the ass cancer?
我就直说了吧 Woody
I'm not going to sugarcoat it, Woody.
我发现了一些值得警醒的东西
I found something alarming in there.
不
No!
这个啊 我不小心坐上面了
Oh, yeah, I accidentally sat on that.
是嘛? 这些也是吗?
Really? These too?
1978年冠军
好像有人在自己屁股里开甩卖会呢
Looks like somebody fell ass-first into a yard sale.
我是有条理的人嘛 这叫"后庭风水学"
I just like to be organized. I call it bung-shui.
恶搞风水学"Feng Shui"
除了肠壁轻微撕裂
Besides some mild tearing
电影《查理和巧克力工厂》中制作巧克力的小矮人
还有一个我肯定是呜巴鲁巴小矮人的东西 没能成功抓出来
and what I swear was an oompa loompa I was never quite able to get a hold of,
你没啥事了
you're all clear.
真棒
Great.
现在 把这些东西塞回我屁股 我就走人啦
Now, if you'll kindly Return those things to my ass, I'll be on my way.
Woody 你麻醉劲儿还没过呢
Oh, Woody, you're still under the influence of the anesthetic.
我不能让你一个人开车回去
I can't let you drive yourself home.
我不是给了你好几个紧急联系人电话
I gave you a bunch of emergency contacts.
没给他们打电话吗?
Didn't you call 'em?
打了 有四个是空号
Yes. I got four wrong numbers,
三个直接挂了 还有一个要"干我娘"
Three hang-ups, and a "[bleep] my mother."
她老人家都死三年了 这事估计很困难
She's been dead for three years, so that would be difficult
但也不是没可能
But not impossible.
好吧 你看怎么办吧
Okay. So what does this mean?
从医学角度来看? 你没朋友啊
Medically speaking? Well, you have no friends.
因为没人能来接你
And since there's no one here to pick you up,
我只能撂倒你了
I'm going to have to put you down.
等下等下 我就不能叫辆出租车吗?
Wait, wait! Can't I just call a cab?
这我倒是没想到
Hmm, I never thought of that.
看来我过去撂倒那么多人是多此一举了
Guess I didn't need to put all those people down after all.
天 我都脸红了
Boy, is my face red.
开玩笑的 我没感情的
Kidding! I can't feel emotion.
快放我出去
Get me out of here!
Tommy 闭嘴 老实吹你的长号
Tommy! Shut up and play your trombone!
漫迪字幕组倾情奉献
脆莓公园
♢ 白云苍狗 ♢ 偏执绝非过错
♢ 井脑湿 ♢ MaxPayen999
♢ 旗木 联合译制
你这胸毛还真像烤焦的墨西哥卷肉馅呢
Wow, your chest hair really does look like burnt taco meat.
我就说嘛
I told you.
我下边的毛毛像奶酪丝呢
My pubies looks like cheese curls.
等下 这些就是奶酪丝
Oh, wait, these are cheese curls!
等等 不是
Oh, wait. They're not.
你们都把我说饿了
You guys are making me hungry.
嗨 我是来找"毛茸茸性饥渴处子"的
Hi, I'm looking for the "hairy, horny, hung virgin."
太好了 太好了 太好了 太好了
Oh, boy, oh, boy, oh, boy, oh, boy, oh, boy!
闭嘴 Connie 她是来找我的
Shut up, Connie. She's here for me.
你是头熊?
You're a bear?
你之前从没说过你是熊啊
You never mentioned that you were a bear.
- 你欺骗我 - 欺骗?
- You lied to me. - Lied?
你可是看了Craigslist上的广告找上门的 我没杀你算不错了
You answered an ad on Craigslist. You're lucky I'm not murdering you.
Craigslist: 美国分类广告网站
好吧 我还是不约了
Well, we're not having sex.
那就谋杀
Murder it is.
♪ Malloy没有妹子约 ♪
♪ Malloy can't get laid! ♪
♪ Steve得了狂犬病 ♪
♪ Steve has rabies! ♪
我没...
No, I--
等一下 真奇怪
Wait a second, that's weird.
Malloy 再咬一口 这次使点劲
Malloy, bite him again. But harder this time.
啥?
What?
好棒 咱们互相开吃吧
Yay! Let's eat each other!
我要吃Ethel
Dibs on Ethel.
有意思
Fascinating.
Malloy 你嘴里有四颗门牙
Malloy, you have four incisors.
你嘴里还有J8味呢
And you have dick on your breath.
知道这意味着什么吗?
Do you know what that means?
你老爹来过了?
Your dad's in town?
不是 这说明你是一种很稀有的熊
No, it means you're a rare breed of bear.
可能是这个族群最后一只活体
You may even be the last one alive.
多嘴熊
Ursus loquacious.
多嘴熊? 他不是在猎鹰队效力呢么
Ursus Loquacious? He plays for the Falcons.
Denzel误听
你们特么为啥都给我假电话号码?
Why the hell did you all give me fake contact numbers?
你们可真够朋友
Some friends you are.
朋友? 我们都不怎么喜欢你
Friends? We don't even like you.
为毛啊?
Huh? Why?
很简单 你丫就一混球
Simple. You're an asshole.
睁眼说瞎话 贱人
That's not true, bitch.
Woody 能给我换套新制服吗? 我又穿崩了一件
Woody, can I get a new uniform? I outgrew another one.
去你大爷的 肥逼 老子不会再掏钱给你买制服了
[bleep] you, lard ass. I'm not buying you another uniform!
减减肥 或者最好在脑袋上开一枪 一坨死肥膘的泼猴翔
Lose some weight, or better yet, blow your brains out, you fat tub of monkey shit!
说真的 你们真觉得我是混球?
Honestly now, you guys really think I'm an asshole?
Epstein鸡尾酒吧
真不敢相信我居然一个朋友都没有
Oh, I can't believe I don't have any friends.
没人懂我
Nobody gets me.
再来一杯肉桂甜酒
One shot of goldschlager.
还以为地球上就我一人爱喝肉桂甜酒呢
I thought I was the only one who enjoyed goldschlager.
开什么玩笑
You kidding?
这可是12刀以内能买到最好的带金箔的烈酒了
This' the finest gold-flecked schnapps that money can buy for under $12 a bottle.
肉桂甜酒出产自瑞士 酒瓶中含有24克拉金箔
有一回我喝了太多这玩意儿
One night, I drank so much of this stuff,
一下从稀屎里淘出了80刀的金子
I panned my diarrhea, and I made $80.
这可能是我听过最牛X的事
That might be the most awesome thing I've ever heard.
Todd Ford市长
Mayor Todd Ford.
褐丘镇的瘾君子市长?
The crackhead mayor of Hazelhurst?
别听媒体瞎逼逼
Ah, don't believe the media.
那都是他们给我编的外号
They just gave me that nickname
因为我抽大麻停不下来
Because I smoke crack all the time.
Woody Johnson
Woody Johnson.
脆莓公园的抖S林警头头儿?
The whore-punching head ranger of Brickleberry?
谁说不能给自己编外号了?
And they say you can't give yourself a nickname.
酒保 再来一杯
Barkeep, another round!
我兄弟说他要再来一杯
My friend said he wanted another drink!
我去 你冷静点 当心他报警
Oh, shit, you better chill out before he calls the cops!
我可是市长 警察都是给我打工的
I'm mayor. The cops work for me.
今晚免单
Drinks are on the house!
敬我们开启了这段深厚友谊
To the start of a beautiful friendship!
警署
证物室
毒品证据
救火啊 救火
Help! Help!
Malloy 有个天大好消息
Malloy, I have amazing news.
我做了一些调查 结果发现...
I did some research and found out--
你并不是你们族群的最后一只
You're not actually the last of your species.
原来还有一只呢 而且是母的哦
Turns out there's one more, and it's a female!
话茬儿接得不错啊 Connie
Way to step on my dick, Connie.
抱歉
Sorry.
我把那只熊引进到脆莓野生动物保护区了
I'm having the bear flown into the brickleberry wildlife sanctuary,
好方便你们俩延续物种
So you can continue the species.
我看自己愿不愿意鸟你哈 不愿意呢
Let me check to see if I give a shit. I don't.
知道这意味着什么吗?
You know what this means?
- 这意味着... - 你能和她滚床单了
- It means-- - You get to have sex with her!
而且不止一次哦 要滚到精尽熊亡呢
And not just once, as much as you possibly can.
- 接你妹啊 Connie - 抱歉
- God damn it, Connie! - Sorry!
有点意思
Interesting.
跟我好好说说这"滚到精尽熊亡"的好事儿呗
Tell me more about this "having sex as much as I possibly can."
好吧
All right.
不过首先 你要学一套复杂的交配仪式
Oh, but first, there's a complex mating ritual that you're gonna have to learn.
这样 你要围在她身边绕七圈
Okay, now, you circle around her seven times,
她的阴唇就会鼓胀起来
And her labia will become engorged.
没错
Check.
没见过这么操蛋的动物假扮派对
This is the worst furry party ever.
然后你开始低吼 再一把抓住母熊的屁股蛋
And then you begin to growl and cup the buttocks of the female...
我可能要拉到熊服里了
I think I just lost my deposit on this bear suit.
我不明白 Denzel 为啥你一直这么苗条?
I don't get it, Denzel. How do you stay so thin?
我光做爱就消耗不少热量呢
I burn a lot of calories having sex.
自己打手枪能消耗热量吗?
Does it work if it's with yourself?
不能
No.
像我这样的混球一定混到没朋友是吧?
I don't have friends 'cause I'm an asshole, huh?
头发长见识短 老子交到一个比我混球一百倍的家伙做朋友
See what you know, I made a friend who's a bigger asshole than me!
Daniel Tosh?
本剧制片人兼Malloy配音
谁? 他是哪根葱
Who? Never heard of him.
不 我的好基友是地球上最牛X的人物:
No, my B.F.F. Is the coolest guy on the planet:
Todd Ford市长
Mayor Todd Ford.
真的吗 Woody? 他又贪污又嗨毒
Really, Woody? He's a corrupt drug addict.
人家才不嗨毒嘞
He's not a drug addict.
拿到嗨药咯
I got the drugs!
证据
给我 给我 快给我
Gimme! Gimme! Gimme!
千万不能让这些冰毒流到街头上去
We've gotta keep this meth off the street.
我没事
I'm all right.
他没事的 昨晚我都这样搞过三次了
He's fine, I had to do this three times last night.
感觉嗨翻天了
I feel awesome!
我是不是又挂了?
Did I die again?
"我是不是又挂了?" 爱死这哥们了
"Did I die again?" I love this guy!
搞得我都想当市长了
Makes me want to be mayor.
话说 今晚有何节目?
So, what are we doing tonight?
有的 我要和一些达官显贵的朋友们去打牌
Ooh, yeah, me and some high-powered friends are playing poker,
不过这种赌局对你来说可能筹码太高
but it might be a little too high-stakes for you.
开什么玩笑? "筹码高"可是我的中名
You kidding? High-stakes is my middle name.
好吧 Woody 既然你诚意满满
All right, Woody, if you insist!
♪ 今晚就让我们嗨翻天吧 ♪
♪ We're going to party tonight! ♪
脆莓野生动物保护区
记住 整个族群的延续就全靠你们俩了
Now remember, the continuation of your entire species depends on this.
开始吧 把爱猛烈地做起来吧
Here we go. Let the banging begin.
你好
Hello.
算了 省省吧 休想让我干这货
Nope. No way. I am not [bleep] that.
你不能走啊
You can't leave.
你们族群就靠着你们俩交配来延续了
Your species depends on the two of you mating.
是啊 Malloy 她也不赖的
Yeah, Malloy, she's not that bad.
是啊 她看起来像个影星呢
Oh, yeah, she looks like a movie star.
美国老牌男影星
弹珠眼有如史蒂夫·布西密 龅牙有如...
Steve Buscemi's eyes and the teeth of...
还是史蒂夫·布西密
Steve Buscemi.
去你大爷的 弃牌
God damn it! I fold.
首播于2012年的HBO剧集
自打恶补过《衰姐们》第一季后
I haven't seen this many unnecessary folds
fold含有"弃牌"和"分手后复合"双意
《衰姐们》女主多次与男友分手后复合
我就再没见过这么多次贱逼复合了
Since I binge-watched season one of Girls.
你看起来是个猎人 对吧 Ford?
So, you're a bit of a hunter, eh, Ford?
我确实喜欢猎杀野兽
I do love big game hunting.
只可惜这附近没有能让我游猎的地界儿
It's too bad there's no good place to do it around here.
是啊 天杀的奥巴马 把珍奇异兽都弄到非洲去了
Yeah, [bleep] Obama, Putting all the good animals in Africa.
不管怎么说 谢谢邀我来把你们的钱都赢个干净 朋友们
Anyway, thanks for inviting me and letting me take all your money, fellas.
还有你 布鲁斯·詹那
And you, Bruce Jenner,
前美国运动员 奥运冠军 多次整容
你要么是个盖世丑男
You are either a very ugly man
- 要么就是个绝色美女 - 谢谢你
- Or a very attractive woman. - Thank you.
布鲁斯是输牌太多 输成不男不女的
Actually, Bruce lost a lot of poker games.
最开始他赌"输了就穿裙子"
The first bet was "wear this dress,"
后来赌"输了就吃雌激素药" 然后就一直这么输赌下去
and then it was "take these estrogen pills," and so on and so on.
你乐意让这手牌来得更刺激些吗 Woody?
Would you care to make this hand a little more interesting, Woody?
来啊 来啊 我是说... 来看看咯
Yes! Yes! I mean...Eh, maybe.
你想和我赌什么?
What do you have in mind?
我知道你做梦都想当市长
Well, I know your dream job is to be mayor.
不如这样 如果你赢了 你就当市长?
How about, if you win, you get to be mayor?
如果我赢了 脆莓公园就是我的
If I win, I get control of Brickleberry.
这样真的好吗?
Oh, I don't know.
怎么了 Woody? 蛋都吓碎了嘛?
What's the matter, Woody? Got no balls?
想借我的蛋用不?
You want to borrow mine?
在格兰岱尔市的垃圾车里呢
They're in a dumpster in Glendale.
加州西南部城市
那么 Woody 你是选择拼一回呢
So, Woody, are you going to take the bet,
还是不够胆做我的朋友呢?
Or are you not man enough to be my friend?
我出牌 四个老A齐上阵
All right, I'm in! Four aces.
手气不错嘛 但是你如何斗得过我的...
That's an impressive hand, but does it beat my...
同花顺?
Straight flush?
见鬼
Oh, shit.
居然因为同花顺把公园给输掉了
I lost the park to a straight flush!
哥早悲伤逆流成河了 我老二都给一对基佬赢走了
Cry me a river. I lost my dick to a pair of queens.
喂 我们有名有姓的好吧
Hello! We have names, you know.
一次
One.
好了 我跳了绳 还做了半个仰卧起坐
Okay, I jumped the rope, I did half a sit-up.
为啥就没减下去呀?
Why can't I lose weight?
这些时我吃的都只有这些年糕啊
All I've been eating are these rice cakes.
这些都是甜米饼 蠢货
Those are rice krispie treats, dumbass.
早上好 林警们
Morning, rangers!
昨晚我一不小心玩大发了...
So, I got a little overextended last night
在牌桌上把公园输给市长了 换个话题
And, uh, lost the park to the mayor in a poker game. Moving on.
你做了啥?
You what?
别怨我 我手头有四张老A
Don't judge me. I had four aces.
换成是你们都会这样做
All of you would've done exactly the same thing,
因此你们在这事上和我的责任相同
So this is as much your fault as it is mine.
看吧 Woody 这就是为什么没人喜欢你
See, Woody, this is why no one likes you.
你以为他就因为这样才讨人嫌?
You think that's why no one likes him?
别担心啦 公园不会有事的
Oh, don't worry about it. The park will be fine.
太阳依旧从东边升起
Nothing's going to change.
能在自家后院猎杀野生动物再方便不过了
It's going to be so much more convenient to hunt them all in our own backyard.
好吧 这样也好
Well, this is great.
野生动物肯定能招来大批游客
All these wild animals are going to be a huge draw for the tourists.
呃 Woody
Uh, Woody,
野生动物正在吃游客哎
The animals are eating the tourists.
我刚想到了一个帮你减肥的好方法
I just thought of a great way for you to lose weight.
真的?
Really?
我称之为"能特么跑多快就特么跑多快"减肥法
It's called running as fast as you mother[bleep] can!
最糟也不过是它们撕断了你的腿
Worst-case scenario, they rip your leg off.
腿没了正好减肥了
That's still losing weight!
谢啦 好兄弟
Thanks, buddy!
Woody 你要怎么解决这摊子事?
Woody, what are you going to do about this?
你接受"草泥马"这个回答吗?
Hmm, would you accept "[bleep] you" as an answer?
不
No.
那行 老子去找市长谈
Fine! I'll go talk to the mayor.
不好啦 Bobby 有犀牛
Oh, no, Bobby. Rhinoceroseses!
我早说我们不该玩"尤曼吉"的
I told you we shouldn't have played Jumanji!
电影《勇敢者的游戏》游戏棋 游戏内容会成真 这里恶搞了片中"万兽奔腾"的一幕
求你啦 Ford仔 我们谈谈好么?
Listen, Fordles, can we talk?
部分其他林警... 当然 不包括我...
Uh, some of the other rangers-not me, of course--
觉得你空运来的动物们正在...
Think the animals you flew into the park are
毁掉公园 无稽之谈 对吧?
destroying the place. Crazy, right?
告诉他们脆莓现在我说了算
Tell them I'm calling the shots at Brickleberry now.
如果真毁了 也没啥大不了
If it gets destroyed, so be it,
只要我可以猎杀动物
as long as I get to hunt down
用真汉子唯一该用的方式送它们上路:
and kill those animals the only way a man should...
嗑嗨大屠杀
High on crack!
那为什么你偏偏要在脆莓这样搞?
Yeah, but why do you have to do it at Brickleberry?
这比去非洲强多啦 老子讨厌坐飞机
Well, it beats going to Africa. I hate flying.
还有那些皮包骨的大肚娃儿真是吓死我
And skinny kids with fat bellies scare me.
实为腹积水病症
我跟你想的一样
I know, right?
选个体型好吧 既胖又瘦的死畸形们
Pick a body type, you fat skinny bastards.
我真庆幸当时发牌你一连抓起了两张A
I'm just lucky you picked up those two aces on the draw.
是啊 如果我...
Yeah, if only I'd--
你怎么知道发牌时我抓了两张A?
how'd you know I picked up two aces on the draw?
等一下 你出老千
Wait a second. You cheated!
哎哟不好啦 搞政治的居然出老千?
Oh, no. A politician who cheats?
接下来会怎样?
What's next?
来个搞椰子的爱斯基摩人吗?
An eskimo that [bleeps] coconuts?
不好意思 嗑太嗨了
Sorry, I'm very high.
可... 可我们是好基友啊
But--but we're best friends.
我们才不是 你是个混球
We're not friends! You're an asshole!
我像玩婊子一样玩弄了你 为的就是把公园搞到手
I played you like a bitch just to get my hands on that park.
咱开战了 你现在是Woody Johnson不同戴天的仇人了
This means war! You are now a sworn enemy of Woody Johnson.
除非你想咱俩从头来过重归于好?
Unless you want to start over and try to be friends again?
我不想
No, I don't.
老天爷 这烂剧本谁写的?
Jesus, who wrote this shit?
而且呀 他可以日椰子
And then, he could [bleep] a coconut!
编锯室 (二人配音为本剧两位主创)
艾美奖俺来啦
Hello, Emmy.
美国电视界最高奖项
脆莓野生动物保护区
出来嘛 Mallory
Come on out, Mallory.
别害臊哦
Don't be shy.
当丑逼的心情我懂
I know what it's like to be the ugly one.
但慢慢会好起来的
But it gets better.
根本不会好起来
It doesn't get any better.
这个我搞得定
I can work with this.
脆莓野生动物保护区
Ethel Connie 老实说 干得漂亮
Ethel, Connie, gotta say, nice work.
看得我都硬起来一半了
I actually have half a chub here.
那啥 Mallory 你好安静啊
So, Mallory, you've been quiet.
跟我聊聊你自己吧
Tell me something about yourself.
自然表现就好 Mallory
Be yourself, Mallory.
想骑着姐逍遥一下么?
Wanna take this train to [bleep] town?
你说啥?
I'm sorry?
射点出来让姐尝尝好么?
Can I taste yo' juice?
我都不敢确定我们在谈什么话题
I'm not even sure what we're talking about.
姐想一拳伸进你菊花
I want to punch you in the b-hole.
我够了
All right.
今天的关键词是"绝种"
And the word of the day is "extinction."
把姐倒挂起来 用你蛋蛋蹭姐的双峰
Hang me upside down and speed bag my tits!
我的好基友背叛了我
Oh, my best friend betrayed me,
怎么夺回公园 我一点办法都没
and I have no way of getting my park back.
- 我该怎么办 Malloy? - 我也有自己的麻烦
- What do I do, Malloy? - I got my own problems.
有个斜眼儿小荡妇想让我拳交她的菊花
Some cock-eyed woodchuck wants me to punch her in the b-hole.
难怪这个物种只剩下我一个
No wonder I'm the last of my species.
有啦 你真是天才 Malloy
That's it. You're a genius, Malloy.
我不是 但我还是可以让Steve蠢得赛过一麻袋干翔
No, but I still make Steve look dumber than a sack of dry shit.
sack有"麻袋"和"蛋蛋"双意
"麻蛋"
Sack.
Malloy 你干嘛遛掉啊?
Malloy, why'd you run off?
我觉得你和Mallory刚对上眼儿呢
I thought you and Mallory had a real moment there.
你指的是哪个眼儿?
What moment was that?
她让我用拳搞的那个"眼儿"么?
When she asked me to fistfight her lady lips?
是呀 真特么够劲
Yeah, that was [bleep] hot.
Malloy 延续你的种群 你义不容辞
Malloy, you have a responsibility to continue your kind.
你必须和她啪啪啪
You have to have sex with her.
我不如去死
I'd rather die.
那你让我别无选择了
Then you leave me no choice.
我开玩笑的
I wasn't serious!
好萌的昏迷样儿啊
Aw, what a cute little coma.
你这是干嘛?
What are you doing?
昨晚我从Mallory那里取到了一颗卵子
I was able to extract an egg from Mallory last night.
现在只要搞到Malloy的精子 就可以人工授精了
Now I just need to get Malloy's sperm, and I can fertilize it.
精子
没事的 Ethel 只要闭上眼睛
It's okay, Ethel. Just close your eyes
假装你又在为逃掉超速罚单 帮交警卖力撸管
And pretend you're tugging your way out of another speeding ticket.
Connie 搞到精子啦
Connie, I got the semen!
总算出来了
Yeah, it's about time.
我光是看了两小时都看累了
I got tired of watching after two hours.
跟撸麻醉管儿相比 撸醉鬼的管儿简直不叫事
Yeah, whiskey dick's nothing compared to tranq spank.
我肯定得腕管综合症了
Pretty sure I have carpal tunnel now,
健康提示: 过长时间打游戏 打字 撸管是腕管综合症的成因
但知道吗 这么做也值了
But you know what, it was worth it.
Steve 你又涨了9斤
Steve! You gained 10 pounds!
我靠 这衣服我永远都穿不上了
Damn it! I'll never fit in this uniform.
看来节食和锻炼都不适合你
Looks like diet and exercise aren't your thing.
咱们得试些新花样
We need to try something new.
可我啥都试过了 连抽脂都不行啊
But I've tried everything. Not even liposuction worked!
难以至信你们居然要把这些好东西扔了
I can't believe you were going to throw this out.
好吃死了都
It's delicious!
你要带我去哪儿?
Where are you taking me?
我在梦里正被撸得飞起呢
I was having the best tug job dream.
你得帮助我夺回这个公园 给我安静点
You're going to help me save this park. Now be quiet.
大象JJ落在了象牙位置
市长 这款象牙你偷得有一套呀
Well, mayor, I guess you really tickled his ivories.
你要干嘛 Woody?
What do you want, Woody?
你说自己是个赌徒嘛
Well, I thought you might be interested in a little wager,
我想我有你感兴趣的东西
Since you call yourself a betting man.
你还能有什么可赌的?
What could you possibly have that I want?
我已经把你所有的东西都夺走了
I've already taken everything from you.
不是所有东西喔 看看这货牙口
Oh, not everything. Look at these gums.
这是在演《根》吗?
What is this, roots?
反映美国蓄奴制时期的电影 片中有奴隶主看奴隶牙口叫价的场景
哇 多嘴熊
Oh, my god! Ursus loquacious!
世界上最稀有的动物
The rarest animal on the planet,
圣品啊
The holy grail.
赌局这么玩
Here's the bet.
- 我让你拿Malloy打猎 - 什么?
- I'll let you hunt Malloy... - What?
但只给你一个小时
But only for one hour.
如果你杀不了它 就把公园还给我
If you can't kill him, I get my park back.
你能不能想个不让我死的点子啊?
Can we think of a plan that doesn't involve my death?
那太麻烦了
Nah, too much trouble.
狩猎明天中午开始
The hunt starts at noon tomorrow.
成交
You got a deal.
我打算搞定那头犀牛呢
Get ready to mount that rhino.
排队等着去吧 我喜欢这个外来妞
Get in line. Oh, I like these exotic women.
节食饿死我了
Ugh! This diet is making me hungry.
不知道这个"米青子"是谁 我要吃这酸奶了
I don't know who see-mon is, but I'm eating his yogurt.
Steve饿昏看错"精子"
我要吃个底朝天
It's got a kick to it!
Steve 你特么干什么呢?
Steve, what the [bleep] are you doing?
我知道 我破了节食的规矩了
I know! I'm cheating on my diet.
什么叫破规矩了? 你吃的是熊的精液
Cheating on your diet? You eating bear jizz!
天啊
Oh, my god!
"米青子"为啥要把名字写在装熊精液的杯子上啊?
Why would see-mon write his name on a cup of bear jizz?
Steve 你还好吧?
Steve, do you feel okay?
我吃了点不干净的酸奶
Uh, just got a hold of some bad yogurt.
正努力忘掉这糟心事呢
I'm trying not to think about it.
要不要来点木薯布丁?
Wanna split my tapioca pudding?
你说"不要"就可以了
You could've just said "no."
Woody的超级计划是牺牲我的性命...
So Woody's big plan is to sacrifice my life
换回这个破公园
To get his stupid park back.
毛绒小熊熊 爸爸不会让你死的
Cubsy wubs, there's no way daddy's gonna let you die.
我都计划好了
I've got it all planned out.
计划什么 我的葬礼吗? 吃我精液去吧 Woody
What? My funeral? Eat my jizz, Woody.
闭嘴
Shut up!
首先 我要用熊脚印把Ford市长引到荆棘路上去
First, I'm going use bear tracks to lure mayor Ford to the brickleberry briar patch
这是计划的第一步
where stage one of my plot begins...
然后我们开始计划的第238步:
And that brings us to little ol' stage 238:
蝙蝠侠现身大喊: 正义必胜
Batman'll come swinging in and say, "justice!"
只要我们在中午前布置好 你就没事了
So as long as we do this all before noon, you'll be fine.
现在12点45了
Uh, it's 12:45.
看吧 所以我需要在屁股里塞个闹钟嘛
You see, that's why I need an alarm clock in my ass!
喔 Malloy
Wow, Malloy!
我不知道你也在三个乳头俱乐部
I didn't know you were in the triple nipple club too.
该死 快闪
Oh, crap! Move!
我走了 你这计划真不错
I'm outta here. Great plan, Woody.
你要去哪? 外头太危险了
Where are you going? It's dangerous out there.
这里照样危险
It's dangerous in here.
如果真要死 我不想死的时候还是处男
And if I'm gonna die, I'm not gonna die a virgin.
嘿 有人把漂白粉放到我的蛋黄酱里去了
Hey! Someone spilled bleach in my warm salted mayonnaise.
你闻一下 Steve
You smell it, Steve?
这味道太像...
That's so specifi--
恶心死了
Ew, gross!
脆莓野生动物保护区
没多少时间了 只能咱俩做爱了
There's not much time. We have to make love.
必须啊我擦
Shit, yeah, we do.
该给你亮亮老娘我的底了
Oh, it's time to serve up some panny pudding.
不
No.
我去 你打算在开干之前把我绑起来吗?
Oh, hell, you gonna tape me up before you split these guts?
小心我的洞洞会把你夹死 因为...
That gets my ovaries clapping and my bung hole flapping 'cause--
行了 咱们快点解决吧
All right. Let's get this over with.
出来吧 小熊熊 不会很疼的
Come out, little bear. This won't hurt much.
只是把你小小的灭种而已
It's just a little genocide.
找到你了
I've got you now.
在动物爱爱的时候开枪最爽了
Nothing like killing an animal at his moment of climax.
别碰我的熊
Don't you shoot my bear!
不
No!
我也想体会下失去孩子的感觉
I wish I knew what it was like to lose a child.
克洛伊·卡戴珊: 美国娱乐界明星
布鲁斯·詹那为卡戴珊姐妹继父
你说克洛伊吗?
Khloe?
是 克洛伊 恨死那个长毛怪了
Yeah, Khloe. I hate that hairy ape.
Malloy 你是我最好的朋友 我爱你
Malloy, you were my best friend. I loved you.
真朋友就在身边 我为什么还要去找新朋友?
Why did I try to find a new friend when my true friend was right here,
现在假朋友把我唯一的朋友也杀了
and now my fake friend killed my only friend?
天啊 你个软蛋
Jesus, you're a pussy.
既然你在这儿站着骂我是软蛋
But if you're here calling me a pussy...
这货是... 这啥...
Who is... What is...
天啊 这玩意儿真丑
Ew, god damn it, that's ugly.
她戴个假JJ干嘛?
Why the hell is she wearing a strap-on?
为给你擦屁股 我把自己屁股都奉献出去了
I had to save my ass by giving up my ass.
咱们俩究竟谁是变态 谁心里清楚
Yeah, I'm the only kinky freak around here.
一点 不早不晚 你输了 Woody
1:00 on the dot. You lose, Woody.
我们说的是你得在一个小时里杀掉Malloy
The deal was you had to kill Malloy within one hour.
你杀掉的是另一头丑得要死的熊
You killed another bear who was way too ugly to live anyway.
这回老子算你赢 Woody
I'll give you this much, Woody.
你运气真不错
You sure know how to get lucky.
公园还给你了
The park is yours.
♪ 老子赢了你了 你个混蛋 ♪
♪ I beat you, you son of a bitch! ♪
嘿 Woody
Hey, Woody.
你终于来了啊 蝙蝠侠
Well, look who finally decided to show up-- batman.
你知道他不是蝙蝠侠的对吧?
You do know that's not batman, right?
蝙蝠侠我还不认识?
I think I know batman.
他从我小时候开始
He's been sneaking in my window
每天都爬进我屋里来 用手指插我的蝙蝠洞
and fingering my bat cave ever since I was a little boy.
今天 我对友谊有了新的认识
Today I learned a valuable lesson about friendship.
人最好还是不要交朋友
It is better not to have any friends,
所以我还是接着当个混蛋好了
So I'm just going to continue being an asshole.
另外我刚知道 有个人扮成蝙蝠侠
Oh, and I also learned that some guy dressed in a batman suit
小时候猥亵过我
Molested me as a child.
既然Mallory也死了
Now that Mallory's gone,
很高兴成为本族群里唯一一个活体
I'm pretty excited to be the last of my species.
人们会花大钱来看我的
People will pay big money to see me.
其实你不算最后一个呢 Malloy
Well, you're not exactly the last, Malloy.
我在天拉维上买了个人造熊子宫
Thanks to the artificial bear womb I got on skymall,
Malloy的孩子马上就要诞生了
Malloy's child will be born any second.
哦 我要当爷爷了
Ooh, I'm going to be a grandfather!
Woody 能给我件小点的制服吗?
Uh, Woody, can I get a smaller ranger uniform?
这件太大 我穿不了了
This one doesn't fit me anymore.
天啊 你怎么了?
Oh, jesus. What the hell happened to you?
是不是把所有艾滋染了个遍?
What do you got, all the aids?
不是的 我从吃了Malloy的精液之后 天天都在吐
No, I've been throwing up every day since I ate Malloy's semen.
你干了什么?
You did what?
别担心 我知道你会生气的
Don't worry, I knew you'd be mad,
所以我射了自己的精液进去了
So I replaced it with my semen.
天啊
Oh, my god.
杀了我吧
Kill me!
我杀掉了最后一头 叫我上帝
Got the only one. I am a god now.
这样收场最好了
Uh, that's definitely for the best.
真特么喜欢这家伙
I [bleep] love that guy.